export default {
  name: "Spanish Words: City",
  cards: [
  { front: "bench", back: "(el) banco" },
  { front: "post office", back: "(la) oficina de correos" },
  { front: "apartment", back: "(el) piso" },
  { front: "art gallery", back: "(la) galería de arte" },
  { front: "fire alarm", back: "(la) alarma de incendios" },
  { front: "synagogue", back: "(la) sinagoga" },
  { front: "mosque", back: "(la) mezquita" },
  { front: "fire extinguisher", back: "(el) extintor de incendios" },
  { front: "roller coaster", back: "(la) montaña rusa" },
  { front: "police", back: "(la) policía" },
  { front: "pharmacy", back: "(la) farmacia" },
  { front: "tennis court", back: "(la) pista de tenis" },
  { front: "university", back: "(la) universidad" },
  { front: "zoo", back: "(el) zoológico" },
  { front: "playground", back: "(el) patio de recreo" },
  { front: "supermarket", back: "(el) supermercado" },
  { front: "national park", back: "(el) parque nacional" },
  { front: "warranty", back: "(la) garantía" },
  { front: "police station", back: "(la) comisaría de policía" },
  { front: "farm", back: "(la) granja" },
  { front: "casino", back: "(el) casino" },
  { front: "house", back: "(la) casa" },
  { front: "map", back: "(el) mapa" },
  { front: "gym", back: "(el) gimnasio" },
  { front: "museum", back: "(el) museo" },
  { front: "capital", back: "(la) capital" },
  { front: "bar", back: "(el) bar" },
  { front: "emergency exit (in building)", back: "(la) salida de emergencia" },
  { front: "golf course", back: "(el) campo de golf" },
  { front: "toilet (public)", back: "(el) inodoro" },
  { front: "tourist information", back: "(la) información turística" },
  { front: "temple", back: "(el) templo" },
  { front: "bill", back: "(la) factura" },
  { front: "skyscraper", back: "(el) rascacielos" },
  { front: "park", back: "(el) parque" },
  { front: "souvenir", back: "(el) recuerdo" },
  { front: "swimming pool (building)", back: "(la) piscina" },
  { front: "castle", back: "(el) castillo" },
  { front: "shopping mall", back: "(el) centro comercial" },
  { front: "aquarium", back: "(el) acuario" },
  { front: "town hall", back: "(el) ayuntamiento" },
  { front: "ambulance", back: "(la) ambulancia" },
  { front: "suburb", back: "(el) suburbio" },
  { front: "firefighters", back: "(los) bomberos" },
  { front: "church", back: "(la) iglesia" },
  { front: "water slide", back: "(el) tobogán de agua" },
  { front: "country", back: "(el) país" },
  { front: "fountain", back: "(la) fuente" },
  { front: "market", back: "(el) mercado" },
  { front: "state", back: "(el) estado" },
  { front: "night club", back: "(la) discoteca" },
  { front: "village", back: "(el) pueblo" },
  { front: "water park", back: "(el) parque acuático" },
  { front: "region", back: "(la) región" },
  { front: "restaurant", back: "(el) restaurante" },
  { front: "embassy", back: "(la) embajada" },
  { front: "hospital", back: "(el) hospital" },
  { front: "school", back: "(la) escuela" },
  { front: "factory", back: "(la) fábrica" },
  { front: "football stadium", back: "(el) estadio de fútbol" },
  ],
};
